>> Jem Young: 现在，我要说的是
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And now, I'm gonna
talk about operating system just for
有点过了
a little bit.
我们为什么选择 Ubuntu?
Why do we chose Ubuntu?
有人吗 Ubuntu 是什么 ?
Anybody?
What is Ubuntu?
什么类型的操作系统 ?
What type of operating system is that?
嗯。 >> 扬声器 2: Linux。
Yes.
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Linux.
>> Jem Young: 是的，是 Linux。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yes, it's Linux.
Linux 基于唯一的系统。
Linux is based on the unique system.
我为什么选择 Ubuntu
Just why I choose Ubuntu.
有两种主要的操作系统。
And there's two main types
of operating system.
这里有窗户还有 Unix 的
There's windows and there's Unix based.
他们的工作方式非常不同。
The way they work is very different.
Windows 的概念是 MS DOS。
Windows has this idea of MS DOS.
这就是他们的基本核心。
Which is kind of their underlying core.
它是一个与 Unix 对比的外壳，它是一个在 70 年代设计的系统。
It's kind of the shell you use versus Unix
which is a system designed in 70s 60s.
我不记得它很旧，但 Unix 是 >> 演讲者 3:
I don't remember it's very old but Unix is
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Is in
60 秒 > Jem Young: 60 秒
the 60s
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: 60s
是 >> 演讲者 3: 贝尔实验室
yeah
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Bell Labs
> > Jem Young: 是的，贝尔实验室，是的。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yeah, Bell Labs, yeah.
Bell Labs ，是的，他们说了很多贝尔实验室。
Bell Labs,yeah,
they said a lot whatever the Bell Labs.
不管怎么说都是管理不善
Anyways probably mismanagement.
Unix 不太友好
Unix is not terribly friendly.
Unix 为。
Unix is.
这些书呆子使用的是一种叫 Linux的 Unix 风格。
What the nerds use so
we use a flavor of Unix called Linux.
Linux 非常友好。
Linux is much friendlier.
它一直都是 Linus Torvalds 发明的
It stays up to date as
invented by Linus Torvalds.
因此，名称为 Linux。
Hence the name Linux.
嗯。 也有不同的 Unix 风格
Yeah.
There's also different flavors of Unix.
有 BSD 有 solaris BSD 是一个
There's BSD, there's solaris BSD is a,
向下延伸至 freeBSD。
runs down to freeBSD.
还有我在用的是笔记本电脑
And OSX the laptop I'm using
most you're using here.
它在 freeBSD上运行。
It runs on freeBSD.
所以它是一种 Linux 或 Unix 的风格，与 Linux 不同。
So it's a flavor of Linux or flavor
of Unix, not quite the same as Linux.
但它足够接近我们今天所关心的大部分工具。
But it's close enough for
most tools we care about today.
但我们要用的是 ubuntu
But we're gonna use ubuntu which is.
可以说是最受欢迎的 Linux 发行版。
Arguably the most popular
distribution of Linux.
有 Debian，红帽， fedora。
There's Debian, red hat, fedora.
这里有很多
There's a lot.
这条尾巴就像一个超级隐私的重 Linux 版本。
There's tails which is like a super
privacy heavy Linux version.
有很多 Linux 版本的版本
There's a lot of Linux
versions the great thing about
我想说的是 Linux 是开源的
Linux I'd say vs windows
is it's open source.
所以如果你是这样的话我不喜欢这东西的样子
So if you're like,
I don't like the way this thing looks.
您可以修改它，可以制作自己的版本。
You can modify it,
you can make your own version.
还有一吨的 Linux版本。
And there are a tonne
of versions of Linux.
在 Linux 上面有一吨的鹅绒
There's a tonne of
goodies on top of Linux.
但今天我们不会再利用任何东西了
But today we're not gonna
be using any gooey,
只是笔直的守旧的指挥线路
just straight,
good old fashioned command line.
关于 Linux的任何问题
there any questions about Linux.
因为我们要去潜水
Because we're gonna dive in.
好的。
Alright.
Linux，它的原理是两个。
Linux, it works on the principle of two.
其实就像他们能做的那样简单
It's actually as straightforward
as they can make it.
那是内核
There's the kernel.
内核是与实际机器硬件对话的层。
The kernel is the layer that talks
to the actual machine hardware.
那么 CPU，
So the CPU,
调度所有这些线程的线程技术就是内核所做的
the scheduling all these things threading,
that's what the kernel does.
还有水电费
And then utilities.
今天我们只是利用公用事业
Today we're just using utilities.
我真正喜欢的是 Linux 及其背后的理念
What I really like about Linux and
the idea behind it is instead
把所有东西都烤到操作系统里把所有东西烤到内核里
of baking everything into the operating
system, baking everything into the kernel.
你在烤水电费
You're baking the utilities.
公用事业只是做一件事的小应用程序
Utilities are just the tiny little
applications that do one thing,
一般是一回事
generally one thing.
但由于它们是微小的应用，它们可以更新，
But they're, because they're tiny little
applications, they can be updated and
而不是破坏内核
not break the kernel.
它们只是与内核互动的方法
And all they are is just ways
of interacting with the kernel
与系统上的其他应用程序交互。
interacting with other other
applications on the system.
所以我们今天要做的就是这些公用事业
And so everything we're doing today
is just gonna be these utilities and
它真的是他们发明的一个很棒的模型
it's, really is a brilliant
model that they invented.
这使得所有在 Windows中被烘烤的窗户比窗户更简单。
That makes it much simpler versus windows
where everything's baked into Windows.
因此，如果要更新所有窗口 ( 通常) ，那么您要执行更新。
So you wanna do an update,
if to update all of windows, generally.
所以我们选择 Ubuntu。
So we choose Ubuntu.
切换回过去
Switch back over, and
我们会选择最慢最慢最便宜的服务器
we're gonna choose the lowest,
slowest, cheapest server there is.
你不需要比今天更先进的东西了
You won't need anything more
advanced than that today.
你也许会在未来
You might in the future, but
通常，最好选择您需要的中等级别的类型。
generally, it's better to choose kind
of the medium tier that you need.
然后你可以根据需要向上扩展或向下扩展。
And then you can always scale up or
scale down as you need.
但为了这个我想尽可能的便宜
But for
this I wanna go as cheap as possible.
那么在 7 % 的时间里，没有那一部分吗 ?
So at 7 cent, no was that a fraction of?
这只占一小时的一小部分
It's of a fraction of a fraction
of a cents an hour and
通常计算费用是按小时计算的。
that's generally what compute charge
is charging in terms of hours.
因此，它将每月运行大约 5 美元，因此也不坏。
So it's gonna run about $5 a month,
so it's not too bad.
你应该得到 10 个月的免费贷款
And with the credits,
you should get 10 months free.
如果需要，可以切换到 AWS 或类似的内容。
If you want, you can switch to AWS or
something like that.
但为了学习目的，让我们选择标准。
But for learning purposes,
let's choose the standard.
那之前有多大 ?
And how big is ago?
哇哦 32 号很不错
Wow.
Goes 32 that's pretty impressive.
所有这些都将会有固态驱动器
And all of these are, they're going to
have solid state drive so that means
数据读取的速度要比标准中央计算机快一点
the data read is gonna be a little bit
faster than standard centre computers.
如果我们在记忆中做很多事情，我们也可以选择一些东西。
We could also choose something,
if we're doing a lot of things in memory.
所以如果我们想在记忆中或者类似的事物中进行视频编辑，
So if we wanna do, say, video editing
in memory or something like that,
很多计算方法我们可以选择更多的内存
a lot of compute, we can choose
something with a lot more memory.
但是再次选择标准
But again, choose standard, and
选择最接近您的数据中心区域。
choose the data center region
that's gonna be closest to you.
除非你选择印度班加罗尔 ( Bangalore ) ，否则它不会太重要。
It won't matter too much generally,
unless you choose Bangalore in India.
这只会有点慢点
Which is gonna a little bit slower github.
但我要去旧金山因为如果我在这工作
But I'm gonna go to San Francisco
because if I'm working in that,
那就是我要去的地方
that's where I'm gonna be.
但根据你在世界上选择数据中心的位置
But depending where you are in
the world to choose datacenter,
那就更近了
that's a little bit closer.
我们选择了我们选择的版本是 LTS 版本。
And we choose the version we
chose was the LTS version.
这是长期支持。
That's the long term support.
如果你要制造生产的东西
If you're building things for
production and
不只是事态发展会有很长一段时间
not just developments,
something that's gonna live a long time.
您总是希望选择 LTS 版本。
You always want to choose the LTS version.
说 Ubuntu 19 是有诱惑力的，让我们用这个
It's tempting to say Ubuntu 19 is out,
let's use that instead but
随着时间的推移会有 20 版的版本 20版
that's gonna change over time,
there's gonna be version 20, version 21.
这些命令可能会改变一些
And that the commands
might change a little bit,
事情的安装方式可能有点不同
the way things are installed
might be a little bit different.
但我选择了 LTS 版本，因为这将会有很多年的时间。
But I chose the LTS version because
that's gonna be around for many years.
在 Netflix 上，我们也使用 LTS 版本的节点。
At Netflix,
we use the LTS version of node as well.
这太烂了因为我们不是节点说我们现在支持
Which it kind of sucks because we're
not if node says, Hey, we now support
顶级的水槽等待我无法使用它直到它移动到 LTS 版本为止
top level a sink await I can't use that
until that moves to the LTS version.
但因为我们真正的应用需要很长一段时间
But because we're real application
that needs a live a long time,
我们不呆在流血的边缘
we don't stay on the bleeding edge.
这就是规模的缩减。
That's the downsides of being at scale.
但对于这个阶层来说
But for this class,
我们选择了 ubuntu LTS 版本，因为它会在两年后工作。
we chose ubuntu LTS version because
it'll work even two years from now.